Preliminary Inventory to the Carla A. Hills Papers, 1964-1993
Hoover Institution Archives
- Justice (Box 108)
  - SUPREME COURT OF THE UNITED STATES
    - Taylor v. Hayes (Judge), No. 73-473
    - United States of America, et al. v.
      Connecticut General Insurance Corporation, et al., No. 74-1
    - United States v.
      Connecticut National Bank, et al., No. 73-767
    - United States v.
      Marine Bancorporation, Inc., et al., No. 73-38
    - United States, et al. v. Richardson, No. 72-885
    - United States of America v. State of California, No. 74-739
    - Weinberger, Caspar, Secretary of Health, Education and Welfare v. Eldridge, George H., No. 74-204
    - Weinberger, Caspar W., Secretary of Health, Education and Welfare v. Glodgett, Jean, et al., No. 74-132
    - Weinberger, Caspar, Secretary of Health, Education, and Welare, et al. v. Salfi, Concetta and Kalnins, Doreen A., No. 74-214
    - Weinberger, Caspar W., Secretary of Health, Education, and Welfare v. Weber, William G., No. 74-850
    - Weinberger, Caspar W., Secretary of Health, Education and Welfare v. Wiesenfeld, Stephen Charles, Individually and on Behalf of All Other Pers [UNK] Similarly Situated, No. 73-1892
    - Wheeler, et al. v. Berrera, et al., No. 73-846
    - Wingo (Warden) v. Wedding, No. 73-846
    - Wolff (Warden), et al. v. McDonnell, No. 73-679
  - UNITED STATES COURT OF APPEALS
    - (A) District of Columbis Circuit
      - BRANDON, Robert M. v. SAMPSON, Arthur F., Administrator of the General Services Administration, and General Services Administration, No. 74-1503
      - CONSUMERS UNION OF U.S., INC. v. ROGERS, William P., et al., Nos. 73-1095, 73-1096, 73-1097, 73-1132, 73-1133, 73-1135, 73-1138 (consolidated)
      - INTERNATIONAL ENGINEERING COMPANY, DIVISION OF A-T-O, INC. v. SCHLESINGER, James, Secretary of Defense, et al., No. 74-119
      - KENNEDY, Edward M. v. SAMPSON, Arthur F., Acting Administrator, General Services Administration, et al., Nos. 73-2121; 73-2122
      - KING, Jake v. MORTON, Honorable Rogers C.B., Secretary of the Interior of the United States, No. 73-1995
      - SEA-LAND SERVICE, INC. v. FEDERAL MARITIME COMMISSION and UNITED STATES OF AMERICA, No. 73-2014
      - STOKES, Congressman Louis, et al. v. GENERAL SERVICES ADMINISTRATION, et al., No. 74-1886
      - WASHINGTON RESEARCH PROJECT, INC. v. DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH, EDUCATION AND WELFARE, et al., No. 74-1027
    - (B) First Circuit
      - CORDOVA, Angel L. v. WEINGERGER, Caspar, Secretary of Health, Education and Welfare, No. 73-1353
    - (C) Second Circuit
      - AMERICAN FOREIGN STEAMSHIP CORPORATION v. UNITED STATES OF AMERICA, No. 74-1022
    - (D) Third Circuit
      - BRENNAN, Peter J., Secretary of Labor v. OCCUPATIONAL SAFETY AND HEALTH REVIEW COMMISSION AND HANOVIA LAMP DIVISION, CANRAD PRECISION INDUSTRIES, No. 73-1131
      - LITWICKI, Frank S. v. P.P.G. INDUSTRIES, INC., Nos. 74-1174, 74-1175
      - SYNTHETIC ORGANIC CHEMICAL MANUFACTURERS ASSOCIATION, et al. v. BRENNAN, Peter J., Secretary of Labor and STENDER, John H. Assistant Secretary of Labor for Occupational Safety and Health, No. 74-1129
    - (E) Fourth Circuit
      - ALFRED A. KNOPF, INC., et al. v. COLBY, William, et al., Nos., 74-1478, 74-1479
    - (F) Fifth Circuit
      - FLORIDA, State of, ex rel., Reubin O'D Askew, Governor of [UNK] State of Florida v. TRAIN, Russell E., Administrator of the United States Environmental Protection Agency, No. 74-1790
      - NERO, Zachery Joseph, Bankrupt, UNITED STATES OF AMERICA, v. BERNARD, JR., Rodney, Trustee, No. 74-1520
    - (G) Sixth Circuit
      - N.V. STOOMVAART MAATSCHAPPIJ "DE MAAS" of Rotterdam, Netherlands, a foreign corporation and owner of the M/V THUREDRECHT v. UNITED STATES OF AMERICA and SCOTT MISENER STEAMSHIPS, LTD., of St. Cahterines, Ontario, a foreign Corporation, as owner of the Steamship J.N. McWATTERS v. UNITED STATES OF AMERICA, Nos. 74-1118, 74-1119
    - (H) Eighth Circuit
      - SIOUX VALLEY EMPIRE ELECTRIC ASSOCIATION, INC. v, BUTZ, Earl L., Secretary of Agriculture and HAMIL, David A., Administrator of Rural Electrification Administration, No. 74-1171
    - (I) Ninth Circuit
      - UNITED STATES OF AMERICA v. NEIDORF, Samuel and GLICKMAN, Maria, Executrix of the Estate of Mannes N. Glickman, Deceased, No. 73-2993
  - UNITED STATES COURT OF CLAIMS
    - GROSS, John C. v. THE UNITED STATES, No. 443-73
    - ITT ARCTIC SERVICES, INC. v. THE UNITED STATES, No. 324-73
    - JOHN M. KELTCH, INC. v. THE UNITED STATES, No. 330-72
    - URBANIZADORA SANTA CLARA, S.A. v. THE UNITED STATES, No. 270-74
  - TEMPORARY EMERGENCY COURT OF APPEALS OF THE UNITED STATES
    - GULF OIL CORPORATION v. SIMON, William E., Administrator of the Federal Energy Office, No. DC-24
    - PEOPLE OF THE STATE OF CALIFORNIA, et al., and STATE OF LOUISIANA v. SIMON, William E., et al., No. 9-12
  - SPECIAL COURT, Regional Rail Reorganization Act of, 1973
    - In the Matter of PENN CENTRAL TRANSPORTATION COMPANY, Docket No. 74-8; In the Matter of PENN CENTRAL TRANSPORTATION COMPANY, et al. (Secondary Debtors), Docket No. 74-12; In the Matter of LEHIGH VALLEY RAILROAD COMPANY, Docket No. 74-11; In the Matter of THE CENTRAL RAILROAD COMPANY OF NEW JERSEY, Docket No. 74-6; In the Matter of THE LEHIGH AND HUDSON RIVER RAILWAY COMPANY, Docket No. 74-10
    - In the Matter of PENN CENTRAL TRANSPORTATION COMPANY, Debtor, No. 74-8; In the Matter of THE UNITED NEW JERSEY RAILROAD AND CANAL CO. and Other Secondary Debtors of PENN CENTRAL TRANSPORTATION COMPANY, Debtor, No. 74-12; In the Matter of LEHIGH VALLEY RAILROAD COMPANY, Debtor, No. 74-11; In the Matter of THE CENTRAL RAILROAD COMPANY OF NEW JERSEY, Debtor, No. 74-6; In the Matter of THE LEHIGH AND HUDSON RIVER RAILWAY COMPANY, Debtor, No. 74-10; In the Matter of READING COMPANY, Debtor, No. 74-7; In the Matter of THE ANN ARBOR RAILROAD COMPANY, Debtor, No. 74-9
  - NIXON LITIGATION (Box 119)
    - NIXON, Richard M. v. SAMPSON, Arthur F., BUCHEN, Philip W., KNIGHT, H. Stuart, USDC, D. D.C. No. 74-1518 CONSOLIDATED WITH THE REPORTERS COMMITTEE FOR FREEDOM OF THE PRESS, et al. v. SAMPSON, Arthur F., et al., USDC, D. D.C. No. 74-1533 AND HELLMAN, Lillian, et al. v. SAMPSON, Arthur F., et al., USDC, D. D.C. No. 74-1551 Pleadings #1
    - JACK ANDERSON, Intervenor Re Nixon v. Sampson, et al., USDC, D. D.C. No. 74-1518
    - REPORTERS COMMITTEE FOR FREEDOM OF THE PRESS, et al. v. SAMPSON, Arthur F., et al., USDC, D. D.C. No. 74-1533
    - HELLMAN, Lillian, et al. v. SAMPSON, Arthur F., et al., USDC, D. D.C. No. 74-1551
    - Pleadings #2: CONSOLIDATED ACTIONS re Nixon v. Sampson, No. 74-1518; Reporters Committee v. Sampson, No. 74-1533; Hellman v. Sampson, No. 74-1551
    - Pleadings #3: CONSOLIDATED ACTIONS re Nixon v. Sampson, No. 74-1518; Reporters Committee v. Sampson, No. 74-1533; Hellman v. Sampson, No. 74-1551
    - Pleadings #4: CONSOLIDATED ACTIONS re Nixon v. Sampson, No. 74-1518; Reporters Committee v. Sampson, No. 74-1533; Hellman v. Sampson, No. 74-1551
    - Pleadings #5: CONSOLIDATED ACTIONS re Nixon v. Sampson, No. 74-1518; Reporters Committee v. Sampson, No. 74-1533; Hellman v. Sampson, No. 74-1551
    - Pleadings #6: CONSOLIDATED ACTIONS re Nixon v. Sampson, No. 74-1518; Reporters Committee v. Sampson, No. 74-1533; Hellman v. Sampson, No. 74-1551
    - Pleadings #7: CONSOLIDATED ACTIONS re Nixon v. Sampson, No. 74-1518; Reporters Committee v. Sampson, No. 74-1533; Hellman v. Sampson, No. 74-1551
    - Gray File Box: SUBMISSION PURSUANT TO COURT ORDER OF NOVEMBER 7, 1974 re CONSOLIDATED ACTIONS, to wit: Nixon v. Sampson, No. 74-1518; Reporters Committee v. Sampson, No. 74-1533; Hellman v. Sampson, No. 74-1551 (Box 120)
    - Pleadings #1: NIXON, Richard v. Administrator of General Services and USA, USDC, D. D.C. No. 74-1852
    - Pleadings #2: NIXON, Richard v. Administrator of General Services and USA, USDC, D. D.C. No. 74-1852
    - Pleadings #1: NIXON, Richard v. Hon. Charles R. Richey, USDC, D. D.C. No. 75-1063
    - Pleadings #2: NIXON, Richard v. Hon. Charles R. Richey, USDC, D. D.C. No. 75-1063
  - NIXON LITIGATION (Box 121)
    - HALPERIN, Morton H., et al. v. KISSINGER, Henry A., et al., USDC, D. D.C. No. 1187-73 (Criminal)
    - USA v. MITCHELL, John D., et al., In Re NBC; ABC; CBS; Radio TV News Directors Assn./Warner Communications, USDC, D. D.C. Misc. #74-128
    - USA v. MITCHELL, John M., et al., USDC, D. D.C. No. 74-110
    - OFFICIAL REPRESENTATION: Cases Representing John Mitchell
    - PRESIDENTIAL PAPERS: KOFFLER, Joseph H. v. FORD, Gerald, et al., USDC, E.D.N.Y. No. 74-1406
    - PRESIDENTIAL PAPERS: U.S. Ex Rellative H. JOHN ROGERS v. SAXBE, William B., etc., et al., USDC, D. D.C. No. 74-1455
    - PRESIDENTIAL PAPERS: Motion to Quash Subpoena for Presidential Materials in re OLIVER, R. SPENCER v. The Committee for the Re-election of the President, et al., USDC, D. D.C. No. 1207-73 and DEMOCRATIC NATIONAL COMMITTEE, et al. v. McCORD, Jr., James W., USDC, D. D.C. No. 1233-72
    - PRESIDENTIAL PAPERS: Negotiations on NIXON Papers
    - PRESIDENTIAL PAPERS: Presidential Papers and Other Materials
    - OFFICIAL IMMUNITY: Apton, William H., et al. v. Wilson, Jerry V., et al., U.S. Court of Appeals, D. D.C. No. 73-1614
    - OFFICIAL IMMUNITY: Lowenstein, Allard K. v. Rooney, et al., USDC, E.D.N.Y. No. 74-C-593
    - OFFICIAL IMMUNITY
    - OFFICIAL REPRESENTATION: Sparrow v. Goodman
    - Suits wherein Civil Division Represented President or Aide
    - GSA Regulations regarding Presidential Papers Act
    - Congressional Inquiry re NIXON and Civil Representation of NIXON
    - NIXON Schedule
    - Papers re DRAFT Legislation
    - Research Materials (Archives)
    - Legislation
    - AG Opinion, September 7 Agreement, Buchen's Press Conference Comptroller's Opinion re September 7 Agreement
    - Executive Privilege
    - Options
    - White House Meeting re Documents
    - Depository Agreement and Amendments
    - White House/Special Prosecutor's Office Agreement of, 11/8/74
    - Custody and Security Provisions for Materials
    - Legislation - S.4016, Official Documents Act, Hugh Scott's Statement, Grover Cleveland letter on relations with Senate
    - NIXON Pre-Presidential Papers
    - OTHER NIXON CASES (Nixon Defendant): MASON, Irvin H. v. NIXON, Richard M., USDC, E.D. Va., Alexandria Division, No. 485-74-A
    - OTHER NIXON CASES (Nixon Defendant): SCHULKE, Grant A. and Regina H. v. USA, et al., USDC, D. Colorado No. 74-744
    - Judge Richey's Order and CA Action Thereon
    - CORRESPONDENCE
    - NOTES
    - Transcript of Hearing, October 21, 1974
    - Draft Proposed Findings
    - Draft Affidavits
    - Draft Briefs
    - Draft and Extra Pleadings
- Public Affairs (Box 122)
  - CHRONOLOGICAL MONTHLY DIGESTS OF INVITATIONS, (1975-1976/7)
  - CALENDARS for, 1975 (Box 123)
  - ORIGINAL INVITATIONS, (1975)
    - March
    - April
    - May
    - June
    - July
    - August
    - September
    - October
    - November
    - December
  - CALENDARS for, 1976/77 (Box 124)
  - ORIGINAL INVITATIONS, (1976)
    - January
    - February
    - March
    - April
    - May
    - June
    - July
    - August
    - September
    - October
    - November
    - December
  - CORRESPONDENCE NOTEBOOK A thru Z, (1977)
  - CHRONOLOGICAL MONTHLY FILES, (1975-1976/7) (Box 125)
  - TRIPS FILES (Box 126)
    - Political Trip Itineraries
    - YWCA -- New York City --, 10/8/75
    - NAHRO -- Los Angeles --, 10/13/75
    - Mortgage Bankers -- Chicago --, 10/20/75
    - U.S. League of Savings Association -- AND National Association of Realtors --, 11/11/75 11/12/75
    - Peoria, Illinois Rotary Luncheon --, 3/12/76
    - Detroit --, 4/14/76
    - Flint, Michigan --, 5/13/76
    - AAAA -- Greenbrier --, 5/14/76
    - Habitat --, 5/30/76
    - U.S. Conference of Mayors -- Milwaukee --, 6/29-30/76
    - National Urban, League -- Boston --, 8/2/76
    - Baltimore, Maryland --, 8/6/76
    - Newark, New Jersey --, 8/12/76
    - Kansas City --, 8/76
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania --, 8/25/76
    - Columbus, Ohio --, 9/15/76
    - Indianapolis, Indiana --, 9/22/76
    - Springfield, Illinois --, 9/24/76
    - Ft. Worth, Texas --, 9/28/76
    - Asheville, North Carolina --, 10/1/76
    - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania --, 10/6/76
    - Cleveland, Ohio --, 10/8/76
    - Dallas, Texas --, 10/12-13/76
    - Akron, Ohio --, 10/14/76
    - Albuquerque, New Mexico --, 10/18/76
    - Phoenix, Arizona --, 10/18/76
    - San Diego/San Francisco, California --, 10/19-20/76
    - Seattle, Washington --, 10/21/76
    - San Francisco, California --, 10/25/76
    - Patterson, New Jersey --, 10/28/76
    - Orlando/Jacksonville, Florida --, 10/28-29/76
    - Arden House -- Harriman, New York --, 10/29/76
    - Detroit, Michigan --, 11/1/76
    - Los Angeles, California --, 11/16-18/76
    - World Business Council --, 1/23/77
  - BACKGROUND FILES (Box 127)
    - ACIR (Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations)
    - American College of Trial Lawyers
    - Austin
    - Beame
    - Buchen
    - Buikema
    - Burgess
    - Camp David (1976) Participants
    - Christmas HUD
    - Citizen Participation Training
    - City Club of Chicago
    - Conference on Women & Housing
    - Congressional Hearings
    - Cook -- Life Insurance Lunch
    - Council of Housing Producers
    - Day Care
    - Debro
    - Dolan
    - Dukess
    - Economist Luncheons
    - Edgeworth
    - Energy Resources Council Meeting
    - Fair Housing Month
    - Federal City Council
    - Federal Women's Conference
    - FHA Split Interest Rate Luncheon
    - Ft. Lincoln
    - Gibson
    - Ginzberg
    - Hatch Act -- Political
    - Housing Legislation
    - Housing Problmes
    - HUD Savings Bond Campaign
    - HUD's Women's Groups
    - IDEA (International Downtown Executives Association)
    - International Affairs
    - Jones, Ron -- MHI (Manufactured Housing Institute)
    - Kennedy, Senator Ted
    - Ladies Home Journal
    - Leadership Conference Mtg.
    - Leaman
    - Lynch
    - Lynn
    - Memos
    - Meridian House International
    - National Association of Realtors
    - National Center for Housing Management
    - New England School of Law -- Law Day
    - New York City
    - Newman
    - Oettinger
    - Office of Vice President
    - Palmieri
    - Percy
    - Policy Advisory Board
    - Red Cross
    - Reed
    - Rhinelander, U/S
    - Richardson
    - Russia
    - San Francisco Realtors
    - Seaman
    - Sequoia
    - Shenandoah
    - Stanford Marching Band
    - Tayloe House
    - Travel Authorization
    - Vance
    - Women
    - Women in Passage
    - Women Programs
    - Women's Work -- Homet
  - CORRESPONDENCE NOTEBOOKS, (1976) (Box 128)
    - A
    - B thru BE
    - BO thru C
    - C thru CH
    - CI thru D
    - D
    - E
    - F
  - CORRESPONDENCE NOTEBOOKS, (1976) (Box 129)
    - G
    - H thru HI
    - HO thru I
    - J thru KE
    - KI thru L
    - L
    - MA thru MI
    - MO thru MU
  - CORRESPONDENCE NOTEBOOKS, (1976) (Box 130)
    - MC
    - N
    - PA thru PH
    - PI thru Q
    - RA thru RO
    - RO thru SA
    - SA thru SH
    - SH thru SM
  - CORRESPONDENCE NOTEBOOKS, (1976) (Box 131)
    - SN thru SO
    - ST thru SW
    - TA thru TH
    - TO thru TU
    - TU thru UR
    - VA thru WA
    - WA thru WE
    - WH thru WU
    - Y thru Z
  - CORRESPONDENCE NOTEBOOKS, (1975) (Box 132)
    - A thru Ba
    - Be thru Bo
    - Br thru By
    - Ca thru Cl
    - Co thru Da
    - De thru Dy
    - E
    - F
    - G
  - CORRESPONDENCE NOTEBOOKS, (1975) (Box 133)
    - Ha thru Hi
    - Ho thru Je
    - Jo thru Ke
    - Ki thru Ku
    - La thru Li
    - Lo thru Mc
    - Ma
    - Me thru Mi
  - CORRESPONDENCE NOTEBOOKS, (1975) (Box 134)
    - Mo thru Mu
    - Ne thru Nu
    - Ob thru Ow
    - P thru Q
    - Ra thru Ri
    - Ro thru Ru
    - Sa thru Sch
    - Sco thru Sha
    - Si thru Sn
  - CORRESPONDENCE NOTEBOOKS, (1975) (Box 135)
    - So thru St
    - St thru Sy
    - Ta thru Th
    - Ti thru Tu
    - U thru Ve
    - Wa
    - We thru Wi
    - Wi thru Wy
    - Ya thru Z
- ABA (Box 136)
  - American Bar Association, Antitrust Section
    - ABA National Institute --, 11/8/73
      Private Action in Historical Perspective -- Overviews
    - ABA National Institute --, 11/8/73
      10:15 a.m. -- Private Action -- The Lawyers' View
    - ABA National Institute --, 11/8/73
      11:15 a.m. -- Private Action -- The Corporate View
    - ABA National Institute --, 11/8/73
      12:45 p.m. -- Luncheon
    - ABA National Institute --, 11/8/73
      2 p.m. -- Private Actions -- Purposes Sought/Results Achie
    - ABA National Institute --, 11/9/73
      9 a.m. -- Workshop I: Regulated Industries
    - ABA National Institute --, 11/9/73
      9 a.m. -- Workshop II: Mergers -- Foreign/Domestic Takeov
    - ABA National Institute --, 11/9/73
      11 a.m. -- Workshop III: Emerging Theories -- Attack, Counterattack & Defense
    - ABA National Institute --, 11/9/73
      11 a.m. -- Workshop IV: Handling The Big Case
    - ABA Antitrust Law Journal
      1973 National Institute -- Transcripts
    - ABA National Institute, 1973
      Original Manuscripts
    - ABA 1973 National Institute --, 11/8-9/73 (Box 137)
      Materials to Printer
    - ABA 1973 National Institute --, 11/8-9/73
      Corrected Galleys to Printer
    - ABA 1973 National Institute --, 11/8-9/73
      Corrected Page Proofs
    - ABA 1973 National Institute --, 11/8-9/73
      Corrected Page Proofs to McArdle
  - American Bar Association, Antitrust Section (Box 138)
    - ABA Annual Spring Meeting --, 4/4/74
      9:30 a.m. -- Antitrust/Regulated Industries: Collision Cour
    - ABA Annual Spring Meeting --, 4/4/74
      2 p.m. -- Antitrust/Regulated Industries: Collision Cours
    - ABA Annual Spring Meeting --, 4/4/74
      3:45 p.m. -- Panel Discussion -- Antitrust/Regulated Industrie
    - ABA Annual Spring Meeting --, 4/5/74
      9:30 a.m. -- Part I:
      Antitrust/Proposed Revision of Federal Criminal Laws
    - ABA Annual Spring Meeting --, 4/5/74
      11 a.m. -- Part II: Interview of Lewis A. Engman
    - ABA Annual Spring Meeting
      Washington, D.C. -- April 4-5, 1974
    - ABA Annual Spring Meeting
      Authors' Corrections
    - ABA Annual Spring Meeting
      Printer's Calleys w/corrections
    - ABA Annual Spring Meeting
      Page Proofs to McArdle
    - ABA Annual Spring Meeting
      Photographs
    - ABA Honolulu Meeting -- and Mauna Kea Meeting --, 8/12-14/74 8/17/74
  - American Bar Association, Antitrust Section (Box 139)
    - ABA Antitrust Section -- Publications Committee General, (1972)
    - ABA Publications Committee Antitrust Section Correspondence, (1972)
    - ABA Publications Committee Antitrust Section Correspondence, (1973)
    - ABA Antiturst Law Journal Spring Meeting Correspondence
    - ABA Antitrust Law Journal Spring Meeting Photographs
    - ABA Antitrust Law Journal Annual Meeting Correspondence, (1973)
    - ABA Antitrust Law Journal National Institute -- San Francisco, 11/8-9/73
    - ABA Antitrust Law Journal National Institute -- Photos, 1973
    - ABA Developments Project -- Mullet Bay, St. Maartens, 1974
    - ABA Antitrust Developments, 1971-1972
    - ABA Antitrust Developments Vol. 41, Issue 4 -- Galleys/Proofs, 1971-1972
    - REPORT ON PRICE DISCRIMINATION and FIRST SUPPLEMENT TO ANTITRUST CONSENT DECREE MANUAL
- EXTRAS (Box 140)
  - EXTRA COPIES OF PUBLICATIONS FROM SECRETARY HILLS LIBRARY
    - Antitrust Law Journal, Volume 41, Issue 3
    - Antitrust Law Journal, Volume 41, Issue 4
    - Antitrust Law Journal, Volume 42, Issue 1
    - Antitrust Law Journal, Volume 42, Issue 2
    - Antitrust Law Journal, Volume 43, Issue 1, (6 copies)
    - Antitrust Law Journal, Volume 43, Issue 2, (3 copies)
    - Report on Price Discrimination in Non-Sale and Non-Commodity Transactions
    - American Bar Association Directory, (1973-74)
    - Attorney General of the United States 1971 Annual Report
    - Budget of the United States Government, Fiscal Year 1976 - APPENDIX
    - Budget of the United States Government, Fiscal Year 1977
    - Housing in the Seventies, (2 copies)
    - Housing and Economic Reality: New York City, 1976
    - President's Committee on Urban Housing (Report of) "A Decent Home"
    - Department of Housing and Urban Development, Annual Report, 1973
    - National Growth and Development (Report on), 1974
    - National Governors Conference, States' Responsibilities to Local Governments: "Model Legislation from the Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations"
    - National Governors Conference, States' Responsibilities to Local Governments: "An Action Agenda"
    - Housing and Community Development Act of Public Law 93-383, 1974
    - Summary of the Housing and Community Development Act of, [UNK]
    - Community Development Block Grant Program, A Provisional Report
    - Compliation of the Housing and Community Development Act of (Committee Print), 1974
    - HUD-Space-Science-Veterans Appropriations for 1975, Hearings before Subcommittee of the Committee on Appropriations, House of Representatives, Part 6, Department of Housing and Urban Development
    - Decennial Cumulative Index Monthly Catalog, (1951-1960)
- NEW COMMUNITIES ADMINISTRATION (Box 141)
  Complete set of Board Books prepared by James F. Dausch, Administrator pursuant to request of Secretary Carla A. Hills
- A. Alliance to Save Energy (Box 142-143)
- B. Alliance to Save Energy
- C. Alliance to Save Energy
- Board of Directors Meeting
- D. American Bar Association
  - Section of Antitrust Law Minutes
- E. ABA Minutes
- F. Antitrust Adviser
  - Supplement, 1974
- G. Antitrust Adviser
  - Supplement, 1974
- H. Brookings Minutes
  - Board of Trustees
- A. Farmland Preservation Institute (Box 144-146)
- B. Fraser Associates
- C. Invitations
  - 1., February, 1981 thru April 1981.
  - 2., May 1981, thru June 1981
  - 3., July, 1981 thru September, 1981.
  - 4., October, 1981 thru November, 1981.
  - 5., December, 1981.
- D. President Carter's Reorganization Project. (Binder)
- E. Reagan - Lawyers
- F. Reagan For President
- G. Reagan/Women's Policy Board.
- H. RNC - Target 80's Committee.
- A. ABA - Post Annual Meeting, Keystone Colorado, 1979 8/15-18/79 (Box 147-148)
- B. ABA Institutions
- C. ABA Section of Antitrust Law 1979 Annual & Post-Annual Meeting Council Agenda; Dallas, TX; Keystone, CO, August 12, 1979- August 16-17, 1979
- D. ABA - Annual Meeting; Dallas TX, 1979 8/9-15/79
- E. ABA Fall Council Meeting; Chicago, Illinois, 11/13/79
- F. ABA Annual Spring Meeting Washington D.C., 4/5-6/79
- A. Mid-Winter Mtg. Rio Mar Resort, Puerto Rico, 1/31 to 2/2/79 (Box 149-150)
  - 1. ABA Section of Antitrust Law; Mid-Winter Council Meeting Rio Mar Resort, P.R.; AGENDA (notebook), February 1-2. 1979
  - 2. Suggested Australian Program; David W. Goldweig
  - 3. ABA Section of Antitrust Law; Mid-Winter Council Meeting Rio Mar Resort, P.R., February 1-2, 1979
- B. American Bar Association; Antitrust Law Section
  - 1. ABA Committee/Sub-Committee Projection Reports, 1978/79
  - 2. Committee and Sub-Committee Projection Reports (noteboo, 1978-1979
  - 3. ABA - Post Annual Mtg. Buck Hill Falls, PA., 8/9-11/78
  - 4. American Bar Association Annual Meeting, Plaza Hotel, NY, 8/6-9/78
  - 5. ABA 26th Annual A/T Spring Meeting; Washington, D.C., April 6-7, 1978
  - 6. ABA A/T Section Mid-Winter [UNK] New [UNK] [UNK], 2/12-15/78
  - 7. ABA Council Mtg. Canyon Hotel Palm Springs, 1/27-28/78
- C. ABA Mid-Winter Meeting; Puerto Rico, 1/28-29/80
  - 1. (Blue Binder)
  - 2. ABA - Council Mtg.; Palmas Del Mar, P.R., 1/27-30/80 Mid-Winter
- D. ABA 1980 Spring Mtg.; Washington, D.C. 3/26/80
  - 1. ABA Section of Antitrust Law 28th Annual Spring Meeting Shoreham Americana Hotel; Washington D.C.; AGENDA, March 26, 1980
  - 2. ABA 1980 Spring Meeting
- E. ABA - National Institute; Chicago Illinois, 6/12-13/80